{
    "id": "7e4d7bc3fd1b4a94a45756922b85c4a7",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. start coming on time. (strong obligation)",
            "description": "Must shows strong obligation.",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "will",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………….. pay for this. (threat)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………….. be working late tonight. (weak possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "will",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. spend hours talking to herself. (past habit)",
            "description": "We use would to talk about past ability. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… give credit where it is due.",
            "description": "Ought to shows obligation.",
            "answers": [
                "ought to",
                "will",
                "Can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… the train be on time?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Can somebody help me?’ ‘I …………………………..’ (willingness)",
            "description": "Use will to express willingness. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. I borrow your car? (permission)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Can",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………… not get the job. (possibility)",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "can",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I promise I …………………………. tell anybody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will not",
                "would not",
                "may not"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. you mind my sitting here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Will",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. be here soon. (logical conclusion)",
            "description": "Should expresses logical conclusion. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}